techietake.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy -

**Your Privacy**

We provide a notice to protect your privacy that explains your online information practices you can make the way you collected and used information. For easy finding of this notice we make it available on your homepage. You may request information which is personally identifiable.  
**  
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

To serve ads on the site Google, the third party advertisement vendor use cookies. The use of DART cookies serves adverts to visitors based on their visits to sites on the internet. Tracking users by using DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. Through this http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html URL you can visit content network privacy policy and Google ad. To track users other third parties and ad networks also use cookies. There is no control to IndianOnlineMedia Blogs (IOM) over these cookies. Third parties may use the cookies. 

**Collection of Personal Information**

With the date and time, the IP address access the site will be logged while visiting IndianOnlineMedia Blogs (IOM). It is used to gather broad demographic information, administer the site, track users’ movement, and analyze trends for internal use. It is not linked the IP address to personally identifiable information.  
**  
Links to third party Web sites**

For your reference and use we have included links on this site. The privacy policies on this site are not responsible to us. Keep in mind that the privacy policies may differ from our own. 

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

At our discretion the content may be altered from the statement ay any time. You can contact to this mail@indianonlinemedia.com address if you have any questions about the privacy policy of IndianOnlineMedia Blogs (IOM).
